So in this section you learn that we have two main categories of types in C Sharp on one side we've
Entonces en esta seccin aprendes que tenemos dos categoras principales de tipos en C Sharp
got crosses on the other side we've got structures examples of class those are strings arrays for any
en un lado tenemos cruces en el otro lado tenemos estructuras ejemplos de clase que son matrices de cadenas para
custom classes that you create.
cualquier clase personalizada que crees.
Examples of structures are all the primitive types like integer character float and any custom structures
Los ejemplos de estructuras son todos los tipos primitivos como flotante de caracteres enteros y cualquier estructura
that you create.
personalizada que cree.
The difference between the two types is purely memory management and you can review that again in the
La diferencia entre los dos tipos es puramente administracin de memoria y puede revisar eso nuevamente
lecture hall reference types versus value types.
en los tipos de referencia del aula frente a los tipos de valores.
Now from the next section things start to get really interesting because I'm going to teach you about
Ahora, de la siguiente seccin las cosas empiezan a ponerse realmente interesantes porque voy a
control flow and you'll be able to write simple C-Sharp programs and then in each section you will learn
ensearte sobre el flujo de control y podrs escribir programas simples de C-Sharp y luego en cada
something new about C-Sharp and you'll be able to write more interesting programs.
seccin aprenders algo nuevo sobre C-Sharp y podrs escribir programas ms interesantes.
So I was here the next section
As que estaba aqu la siguiente seccin